;在主畫面下在空白處點擊可以設定任何想打開的檔案，會試著自動抓取封面，也可以在app按右鍵自行設定
;Left-Click empty slot in the main UI to add files. The system will auto-extract icons. You can also Right-Click any icon to manually replace its image.

;在主畫面點滑鼠中鍵可以進deleteApp模式，在deleteApp模式點中鍵會儲存設定並回到主畫面
;Middle-Click in the main UI to enter deleteApp mode. In deleteApp mode, Middle-Click to save your settings and return to the main UI.

;在deleteApp模式下的左下角🖼️相片圖片可以設定主畫面的背景圖片，一樣是左鍵點一下刪除，右鍵設定
;The 🖼️ image icon at the bottom-left in deleteApp mode customizes the main UI background.Left-Click to delete it, and Right-Click to set a new image.

;在deleteApp模式下左鍵點擊App可以直接刪除，點擊完請等待2秒鐘再點下一個(拜託)
;In deleteApp mode, Left-Clicking an App will delete it. Please wait 2 seconds between each click(pretty please).

;在deleteApp模式下的右下角✏鉛筆可以打開詳細設定(就是你現在看的這個txt)
;The ✏ pencil icon at the bottom-right in deleteApp mode opens the advanced configuration (the .txt file you are looking at right now).

;不要刪這個
;Don't delete this
[Variables]

;App縮放大小，最低1，填0.9會變小，推薦1~2之間，填太大會爆炸!，填負數(像是-2)會壞的很好笑
;App hover scale size. Minimum is 1, typing 0.9 will shrink it. Recommended range: 1 to 2. Entering negative numbers like (-2) will be funny.
Zoom=1.2

;當主畫面沒有設定背景圖片（或刪除）時，會顯示此背景顏色。僅支援 (R,G,B) 格式。
;This background color displays when no background image is set (or after it gets deleted). Only supports (R,G,B) format.
SolidColor=0,0,0

;背景顏色的不透明度（Alpha）。推薦設定 1~255（1 為透明空氣，255 為純黑不透明）。在主畫面背景滾動滑鼠滾輪調整
;background opacity (Alpha). Recommended: 1~255 (1=invisible, 255 = solid black). Scroll your mouse wheel over the background in the Main UI to adjust.
BgAlpha=165

;總大小，建議範圍40~300之間，在deleteApp模式下可以把滑鼠移到背景上滾輪設定，任意地方點擊中鍵儲存
;Global Size. Recommended range: 40~300. In deleteApp mode, hover over the background and scroll to adjust. Middle-Click to save.
TileSize=120

;App間距，建議範圍1~2之間，在deleteApp模式下可以把滑鼠移到任意App上滾輪設定，任意地方點擊中鍵儲存
;App Spacing gap. Recommended range: 1~2. In deleteApp mode, hover over any App and scroll to adjust. Middle-Click to save.
Gap=1.3

;App列數，僅支援1,2,3,4,6,8,12,24，在主UI模式下可以把滑鼠移到背景上點擊右鍵切換並儲存
;App Columns per Row. Only supports 1,2,3,4,6,8,12,24. In main UI, hover over the background and Right-Click to toggle.
w=6

;主畫面不支援輸入網址，但在這邊可以手動改網址上去，數字對應App的位置↓
;The main UI doesn't support inputting URLs, but you can manually enter website URLs right here. The number corresponds to the App position ↓
N1=
L1=

N2=
L2=

N3=
L3=

N4=
L4=

N5=
L5=

N6=
L6=

N7=
L7=

N8=
L8=

N9=
L9=

N10=
L10=

N11=
L11=

N12=
L12=

N13=
L13=

N14=
L14=

N15=
L15=

N16=
L16=

N17=
L17=

N18=
L18=

N19=
L19=

N20=
L20=

N21=
L21=

N22=
L22=

N23=
L23=

N24=
L24=
